<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basics on IoT Security Lab Docs</title>
    <link>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basics on IoT Security Lab Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 13:04:57 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/Introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 21:04:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/Introduction/</guid>
      <description>The IoT Securoty Laboratory support GPU accelerated Machine Learning and Deep Learning research workloads. The power of this system is in its multiple state-of-the-art GPUs Nvidia A100 40GB. The IoT Security Laboratory servers are available for UTSA students, faculty and affiliated people to the laboratory. Currently, the only way to access them is through the UTSA Networks, either with a direct connection over WiFi or using the VPN. The system software support anaconda, which allows you to use a wide variety of python modules for different data processing frameworks, such a TensorFlow and PyTorch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access</title>
      <link>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/Access/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 13:04:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/Access/</guid>
      <description>Access to all the systems requires Password Authentication or Public Key Authentication. By default, both options are enable, however, is recommended to use Public Key Authentication. The standard and recommneded method to access is by Secure Shell (SSH). In addition, SSH also includes support for the file transfers utilities scp and sftp. Wikipedia is a good source of information on SSH.
However, you can also access a graphical user interface (GUI) by using the NoMachine app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/FAQ/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 13:04:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/FAQ/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
