<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basics on IoT Security Lab Docs</title>
    <link>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basics on IoT Security Lab Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 13:04:57 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Access</title>
      <link>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/Access/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 13:04:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/Access/</guid>
      <description>Access to all the systems requires Password Authentication or Public Key Authentication. By default, both options are enable, however, is recommended to use Public Key Authentication. The standard and recommneded method to access is by Secure Shell (SSH). In addition, SSH also includes support for the file transfers utilities scp and sftp. Wikipedia is a good source of information on SSH.
However, you can also access a graphical user interface (GUI) by using the NoMachine app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/FAQ/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 13:04:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/FAQ/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/Introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 21:04:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/Introduction/</guid>
      <description>File Systems IoT Security lab servers mounts two shared ext4 file systems (FS) on which each user has corresponding node-specific directories $HOME and $WORK. In the login node, both FS are available, however, in the compute nodes, only the work directory is accessable. There is an alias to traverse between the FS, cdw to go to $WORK.
In addition, there are directories for storing large datasets under /srv/datasets which are globally accesible with read-only permission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/System-Overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iot-security-lab.github.io/basic/System-Overview/</guid>
      <description>System Architecture The IoTSec computations system consists of 2 mainly computing servers divided into nodes. A node is an abstraction to represent a virtual system designated for a specific purpose, for example, the login node which is shared among all users.
Several users may be logged on at one time accessing the file systems. Dozens (sometimes hundreds) of jobs may be running on the login node and the resources are shared and equally divided in a first-come-first-server basis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
